{
  "listado": [
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "el chavo|del 8",
      "pregunta": "1",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "lionel|messi",
      "pregunta": "2",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "pennywise",
      "pregunta": "3",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "star|lord",
      "pregunta": "4",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "wall e",
      "pregunta": "5",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "albert|einstein",
      "pregunta": "6",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "marilyn|monroe",
      "pregunta": "7",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "angus|young",
      "pregunta": "8",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "vito|corleone",
      "pregunta": "9",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "tiger|woods",
      "pregunta": "10",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "john|wick",
      "pregunta": "11",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "carrie",
      "pregunta": "12",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "voldemort",
      "pregunta": "13",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "checo|perez",
      "pregunta": "14",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "freddie|mercury",
      "pregunta": "15",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "amy|winehouse",
      "pregunta": "16",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "muhammad|ali",
      "pregunta": "17",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "lebron|james",
      "pregunta": "18",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "daniel|larusso",
      "pregunta": "19",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "Miercoles",
      "pregunta": "20",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "shaggy",
      "pregunta": "21",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "spike lee",
      "pregunta": "22",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "speed racer",
      "pregunta": "23",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "harry|potter",
      "pregunta": "24",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "Joker",
      "pregunta": "25",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "walter|white",
      "pregunta": "26",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "michael|jordan",
      "pregunta": "27",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "elvis|presley",
      "pregunta": "28",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "miguel",
      "pregunta": "29",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "ed|sheeran",
      "pregunta": "30",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "indiana|jones",
      "pregunta": "31",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "slash",
      "pregunta": "32",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "ant man",
      "pregunta": "33",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "frankenstein",
      "pregunta": "34",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "hannibal|lecter",
      "pregunta": "35",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "stan|lee",
      "pregunta": "36",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "alfred|hitchcock",
      "pregunta": "37",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "shang chi",
      "pregunta": "38",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "Ellen|DeGeneres",
      "pregunta": "39",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "demogorgon",
      "pregunta": "40",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "alex|morgan",
      "pregunta": "41",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "chester",
      "pregunta": "42",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "diego|maradona",
      "pregunta": "43",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "once",
      "pregunta": "44",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "dr strange",
      "pregunta": "45",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "boba fett",
      "pregunta": "46",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "sheldon|cooper",
      "pregunta": "47",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "la mujer|maravilla",
      "pregunta": "48",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "john|lennon",
      "pregunta": "49",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y Celebridades",
      "respuesta": "hermione|granger",
      "pregunta": "50",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "Ironman",
      "pregunta": "51",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "Bono",
      "pregunta": "52",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "Britney|Spears",
      "pregunta": "53",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "tony|hawk",
      "pregunta": "54",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "lewis|hamilton",
      "pregunta": "55",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "roger|federer",
      "pregunta": "56",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "capitan|america",
      "pregunta": "57",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "elsa",
      "pregunta": "58",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "negan",
      "pregunta": "59",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "woody",
      "pregunta": "60",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "daenerys|targaryen",
      "pregunta": "61",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "sonic",
      "pregunta": "62",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "axl|rose",
      "pregunta": "63",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "bella",
      "pregunta": "64",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "Mike|Wheeler",
      "pregunta": "65",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "deadpool",
      "pregunta": "66",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "grogu",
      "pregunta": "67",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "jefe|Wiggum",
      "pregunta": "68",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "Stephen|Curry",
      "pregunta": "69",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "marty|mcfly",
      "pregunta": "70",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "Blossom",
      "pregunta": "71",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "Ojo de|Halcon",
      "pregunta": "72",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "sirius|black",
      "pregunta": "73",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "batman",
      "pregunta": "74",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "daredevil",
      "pregunta": "75",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "lilo",
      "pregunta": "76",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "ahsoka",
      "pregunta": "77",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "Will|Byers",
      "pregunta": "78",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "dr emmett|brown",
      "pregunta": "79",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "rocky|balboa",
      "pregunta": "80",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "Kylo|Ren",
      "pregunta": "81",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "ms marvel",
      "pregunta": "82",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "elton|john",
      "pregunta": "83",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "neo",
      "pregunta": "84",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "cristiano|ronaldo",
      "pregunta": "85",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "froddo",
      "pregunta": "86",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "tom",
      "pregunta": "87",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "bubu",
      "pregunta": "88",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "the wasp",
      "pregunta": "89",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "taz",
      "pregunta": "90",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "rose",
      "pregunta": "91",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "mr bean",
      "pregunta": "92",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "ted lasso",
      "pregunta": "93",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "monica|geller",
      "pregunta": "94",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "ted mosby",
      "pregunta": "95",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "flash",
      "pregunta": "96",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "jon snow",
      "pregunta": "97",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "skeletor",
      "pregunta": "98",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "leon o",
      "pregunta": "99",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Personajes y celebridades",
      "respuesta": "goku",
      "pregunta": "100",
      "categoria": "funkos"
    }
  ]
}
